Guide to the Radio TV Reports Infomercial Collection, 1990-1996 RL.01062
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Original Tapes, 1990-1996; 1
  - Tape 85 - Alpha-Netics Speed Reading--Owen Skousen, Family Channel, 1991 Oct 24, 2:00 AM; Human Calculator--Scott Plansford, Family Channel, 1991 Oct 24, 2:30 AM; Personal Power--Anthony Robbins, Fran Tarkenton, Family Channel, 1991 Oct 24, 3:00 AM; Where There Is a Will There Is an A--John Ritter, Family Channel, 1991 Oct 24, 3:30 AM., 1991-10-24; 82
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 85)
  - Tape 86 - Smart Buyers Network--Hassle Free Way to Buy a Car, WNBC-TV, 1991 Nov 9, 7:00 AM., 1991-11-09; 83
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 86)
  - Tape 87 - Cher's Focus on Beauty--Lori's Hair Care, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 9, 10:00 AM; Deal a Meal, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 9, 10:30 AM., 1991-11-09; 84
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 87)
  - Tape 88 - Blu Blocker Sunglasses--Rapper, WPIX-TV, 1991 Nov 23, 8:00 AM; The Juiceman--Richard Bey, WPIX-TV, 1991 Nov 23, 8:30 AM; Juice Tiger Machine--Jack LaLane, WPIX-TV, 1991 Nov 23, 9:00 AM., 1991-11-23; 85
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 88)
  - Tape 89 - Star Charts--What's in the Stars for You, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 30, 6:00 AM; Relationships Today--Is there Love After Marriage, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 30, 6:30 AM; Inside Track to Fitness--Bob Seagram, Mark Spitz, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 30, 7:00 AM; The Juiceman--John Kordich, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 30, 7:30 AM., 1991-11-30; 86
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 89)
  - Tape 90 - Deal a Meal--Sweating to the Oldies, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 30, 8:00 AM; Personal Power (Changes in Your Life)--Anthony Robbins, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 30, 8:30 AM; Galloping Gourmet--Perfectionnaire Oven, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 30, 9:00 AM; Fit One--Road, Bus, Skiing, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 30, 9:30 AM., 1991-11-30; 87
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 90)
  - Tape 91 - Oster Kitchen Center (appliances)--Graham Kerr, WWOR-TV, 1991 Dec 7, 7:30 AM., 1991-12-07; 88
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 91)
  - Tape 92 - Star Charts--Astrological Guide, WWOR-TV, 1991 Dec 7, 6:00 AM; Deal a Meal--Sweating to the Oldies, WWOR-TV, 1991 Dec 7, 6:30 AM; Today's Family--Modern Medication with Dr, Joyce Brothers, WWOR-TV, 1991 Dec 7, 7:00 AM; Fit One--Trailer, Bus, Skiing, WWOR-TV, 1991 Dec 7, 7:30 AM., 1991-12-07; 89
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 92)
  - Tape 93 - Hooked on Phonics--Chad Murdock, WPIX-TV, 1991 Dec 7, 7:00 AM; Ronco Incredible Inventions (Food Processor), WPIX-TV, 1991 Dec 7, 7:30 AM., 1991-12-07; 90
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 3, Video-cassette Tape 93)
  - Tape 94 - Jane Fonda Lower Body System, WNBC-TV, 1991 Dec 7, 6:00 AM; Blue Tango Lingerie, WNBC-TV, 1991 Dec 7, 7:00 AM., 1991-12-07; 91
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 94)
  - Tape 95 - Jane Fonda Lower Body System, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 2, 6:00 AM; Deal a Meal--Surprise Visit, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 2, 6:30 AM; Making Money--Don LaPrade, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 2, 7:00 AM; The Juiceman, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 2, 7:30 AM., 1991-11-02; 92
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 95)
  - Tape 96 - Hair Club for Men, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 16, 8:30 AM; Fit One--Cross-country Skiing, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 16, 9:30 AM., 1991-11-16; 93
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 96)
  - Tape 97 - The Original 40-Food Robot Processor, WNBC-TV, 1991 Nov 30, 7:00 AM., 1991-11-30; 94
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 97)
  - Tape 98 - Deal a Meal--Pounds Away Plane, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 30, 10:00 AM; Will Your Kid Make the Grade--Michael Landon, WWOR-TV, 1991 Nov 30, 10:30 AM., 1991-11-30; 95
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 98)
  - Tape 99 - Best of Your Hit Parade--Steve Allen Songs from the 40s and 50s, WPIX-TV, 1991 Dec 14, 7:30 AM., 1991-12-14; 96
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 99)
  - Tape 100 - Blu Blocker, WPIX-TV, 1991 Dec 14, No time; The Juiceman, WPIX-TV, 1991 Dec 14, No time; Colorcote 2000--Car Care Polish, WPIX-TV, 1991 Dec 14, 9:00 AM; Oster Kitchen Center--Food processor, WPIX-TV, 1991 Dec 14, 9:30 AM., 1991-12-14; 97
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 100)
  - Tape 101 - Jane Fonda Lower Body System, WNBC-TV, 1991 Dec 28, 6:00 AM; Nordic Flex Gold exercise machine, WNBC-TV, 1991 Dec 28, 7:00 AM., 1991-12-28; 98
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 101)
  - Tape 102 - Nordic Track Ski Machine--Mark Spitz, B, Seagram, WWOR-TV, 1991 Dec 29, 7:00 AM; Slim and Easy Mouth Spray (for weight control)--Ruby Lee, WWOR-TV, 1991 Dec 29, 7:30 AM., 1991-12-29; 99
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 102)
  - Tape 103 - Jane Fonda Workout--The Next Step, WNBC-TV, 1992 Jan 4, No time; St, Go Age Free Skin--Beverly Sills, WNBC-TV, 1992 Jan 4, No time; Milin Method--No Excuses Money Making System, WNBC-TV, 1992 Jan 4, 7:00 AM., 1992-01-04; 100
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 103)
  - Tape 104 - Personal Power--Anthony Robbins, WWOR-TV, 1992 Jan 4, No time; This is Club Med--Vacations, WWOR-TV, 1992 Jan 4, 9:00 AM; Fit One--Cross-country Skiing, WWOR-TV, 1992 Jan 4, No time., 1992-01-04; 101
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 104)
  - Tape 106 - Saturn Automobile, Channel 10, 1991 Apr 18, 11:05 PM., 1991-04-18; 102
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 106)
  - Tape 107 - Golf Breakthrough for the 90s--Pat Summerall and Wally Armstrong, WWOR-TV, 1992 Feb 29, 8:00 AM; The Ultimate Squeeze Juice Machine--Robin Thomas, Molly Fox, Dr, Richard Backrach, 1992 Feb 29, 8:30AM., 1992-02-29; 103
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 107)
  - Tape 108 - Blu Blockers sunglasses, WPIX-TV, 1992 Feb 15, 8:00 AM; The Juiceman, WPIX-TV, 1992 Feb 15, 8:30 AM; Oster Kitchen Center--Graham Kerr juice machine, WPIX-TV, 1992 Feb 15, 9:00 AM; The Juice Tiger--Jack LaLane, WPIX-TV, 1992 Feb 15, 9:30AM., 1992-02-15; 104
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 108)
  - Tape 109 - Nordic Flex Gold exercise machine, WWOR-TV, 1992 Feb 8, 9:00 AM., 1992-02-08; 105
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 109)
  - Tape 110 - Hair Club for Men--Strand by Strand System, Cures for thinning and loss of hair, WWOR-TV, 1992 Feb 15, 12:30 PM., 1992-02-15; 106
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 110)
  - Tape 111 - Colorcote 2000--Car Care Polish, WPIX-TV, 1992 Feb 8, 8:30AM; How to Train Your Dog in only 10 Minutes a Day--Gary Cochran, WPIX-TV, 1992 Feb 8, 9:00AM., 1992-02-08; 107
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 111)
  - Tape 112 - Target---Season with Ginger and Spice; McCoy Media, No station, Undated, No time., 108
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 112)
  - Tape 113 - Nordic Track--The Fit One, WWOR-TV, 1992 Mar 28, 6:00 AM; Golf Breakthrough for the 90s--Pat Summerall and Wally Armstrong, WWOR-TV, 1992 Mar 28, 6:30 AM; Psychic Friends Network, WWOR-TV, 1992 Mar 28, 7:00 AM; The Joy of Juicing, WWOR-TV, 1992 Mar 28, 7:30 AM., 1992-03-28; 109
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 113)
  - Tape 114 - Victoria Jackson--Beauty Breakthroughs II, WWOR-TV, 1992 Mar 28, 6:00 AM; Edgar Morris--Your Face Is Your Passport, WWOR-TV, 1992 Mar 28, 6:30 AM; St, Go of Beverly Hills Age Free Skin, WWOR-TV, 1992 Mar 28, 7:00 AM; Nordic Track--The Fit One, WWOR-TV, 1992 Mar 28, 7:30 AM., 1992-03-28; 110
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 114)
  - Tape 115 - Hooked on Phonics, WPIX-TV, 1992 Mar 28, 6:30 AM; Carlton Sheets Home Study Course, WPIX-TV, 1992 Mar 28, 7:30 AM., 1992-03-28; 111
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 115)
  - Tape 116 - Freedom from Pain--Therapy Plus, WPIX-TV, 1992 Mar 14, 7:00 AM; Bob Mann's Golf Dynamics vol, II, WPIX-TV, 1992 Mar 14, 7:30 AM., 1992-03-14; 112
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 116)
  - Tape 117 - Hooked on Phonics, WPIX-TV, 1992 Mar 21, 6:30 AM; Ronco Drain Buster, Door Saver and Food Dehydrator, WPIX-TV, 1992 Mar 21, 7:30 AM., 1992-03-21; 113
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 117)
  - Tape 118 - Brain Supercharger--Millionaire's Mind, WNBC-TV, 1992 Mar 21, 7:00 AM., 1992-03-21; 114
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 118)
  - Tape 119 - Making of a Commercial, WPIX-TV, 1992 Apr 11, 8:00 AM; The Joy of Juicing, WPIX-TV, 1992 Apr 11, 8:30 AM; Superstep Stairclimber, WPIX-TV, 1992 Apr 11, 9:00 AM; Juice Tiger Machine--Jack LaLane, WPIX-TV, 1992 Apr 11, 9:30 AM., 1992-04-11; 115
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 119)
  - Tape 120 - Golfing Breakthrough for the 90s, WNYW-TV, 1992 Apr 12, 11:00 AM; Body Plus (American Gladiators), WNYW-TV, 1992 Apr 12, 11:30 AM., 1992-04-12; 116
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 120)
  - Tape 121 - Hooked on Phonics, WPIX-TV, 1992 May 9, 6:30 AM; See and Hear Piano Series, WPIX-TV, 1992 May 9, 7:30 AM., 1992-05-09; 117
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 121)
  - Tape 122 - Blu Blocker sunglasses, WPIX-TV, 1992 May 9, 8:00 AM; Win the War Against Acne, WPIX-TV, 1992 May 9, 8:30 AM; Colorcote 2000--Car Care Polish, WPIX-TV, 1992 May 9, 9:00 AM; Superstep Stairclimber, WPIX-TV, 1992 May 9, 9:30 AM., 1992-05-09; 118
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 122)
  - Tape 123 - Cher's Beauty Products, WNBC-TV, 1992 May 30, 7:00 AM., 1992-05-30; 119
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 123)
  - Tape 124 - Whitney Leadership Group, WWOR-TV, 1992 May 31, 12:00 AM; Nu/Hart Clinics, WWOR-TV, 1992 May 31, 12:30 AM; Hair Club for Men, WWOR-TV, 1992 May 31, 1:00 AM; Love Phone--Jessica Hahn, WWOR-TV, 1992 May 31, 1:30 AM., 1992-05-31; 120
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 4, Video-cassette Tape 124)
  - Tape 125 - Getting Rich in America, WNYW-TV, 1992 May 26, 12:30 AM., 1992-05-26; 121
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 125)
  - Tape 126 - Nu/Hart Clinics, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 13, 6:00 AM; Be Your Own Boss, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 13, 6:30AM; Gripmaster, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 13, 7:00 AM; Stepsaver, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 13, 7:30 AM., 1992-06-13; 122
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 126)
  - Tape 127 - Kathy Smith Diet--Fat Burning System, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 13, 8:00 AM; Acne Statin, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 13, 8:30 AM; Hair Club for Men, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 13, 9:00 AM; Fitness Quest--Skiing, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 13, 9:30 AM., 1992-06-13; 123
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 127)
  - Tape 128 - Hooked on Phonics, WPIX-TV, 1992 June 20, 6:30 AM; New Juice Man, WPIX-TV, 1992 June 20, 7:00 AM., 1992-06-20; 124
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 128)
  - Tape 129 - Nu/Hart Clinics, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 20, 6:00 AM; Be Your Own Boss, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 20, 6:30AM; Invisions Hair Restoration, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 20, 7:00 AM; Superstep Stairclimber, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 20, 7:30 AM., 1992-06-20; 125
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 129)
  - Tape 130 - Deal a Meal, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 20, 10:00 AM; Cher's Beauty Products, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 20, 10:30 AM; Psychic Friends Network, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 20, 11:00 AM; Victoria Jackson III, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 20, 11:30 AM., 1992-06-20; 126
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 130)
  - Tape 131 - Deal a Meal, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 13, 10:00 AM; Victoria Jackson, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 13, 10:30 AM; Cher's Beauty Products, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 13, 11:00 AM; Big Green Clean Machine, WWOR-TV, 1992 June 13, 11:30 AM., 1992-06-13; 127
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 131)
  - Tape 132 - Conair Emjoi Twin, WPIX-TV, 1992 July 25, 7:30 AM., 1992-07-25; 128
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 132)
  - Tape 133 - Time Life--The War Years, WWOR-TV, 1992 July 12, 8:00 AM., 1992-07-12; 129
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 133)
  - Tape 134 - Psychic Friends Network, WPIX-TV, 1992 Sep 5, 6:30 AM; Flying Lure, WPIX-TV, 1992 Sep 5, 7:30 AM., 1992-09-05; 130
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 134)
  - Tape 135 - Toastmaster Grillerie, WNBC-TV, 1992 Aug 29, 12:30 PM; Big Green Clean Machine, WNBC-TV, 1992 Aug 29, 1:00 PM; Dura Lube, WNBC-TV, 1992 Aug 29, 1:30 PM., 1992-08-29; 131
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 135)
  - Tape 136 - Deal a Meal, WWOR-TV, 1992 Sep 19, 8:00 AM; Jet Steam Oven--American Harvest, WWOR-TV, 1992 Sep 19, 8:30 AM; Hair Club for Men, WWOR-TV, 1992 Sep 19, 9:00 AM; Charles J, Givens, WWOR-TV, 1992 Sep 19, 9:30 AM., 1992-09-19; 132
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 136)
  - Tape 137 - Carlton Sheets Home Study Course, WPIX-TV, 1992 Sep 12, 8:00 AM; Stair Climber Plus, WPIX-TV, 1992 Sep 12, 8:30 AM., 1992-09-12; 133
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 137)
  - Tape 138 - Time Life--Your Hit Parade with Steve Allen, WWOR-TV, 1992 Sep 12, 6:00 AM; Deal a Meal, WWOR-TV, 1992 Sep 12, 6:30 AM; Hooked on Phonics, WWOR-TV, 1992 Sep 12, 7:00 AM; Jane Fonda, WWOR-TV, 1992 Sep 12, 7:30 AM., 1992-09-12; 134
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 138)
  - Tape 139 - Ross Perot Talks About Jobs, Debt and the Washington Mess, WCBS, 1992 Oct 6, 8:00 PM., 1992-10-06; 135
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 139)
  - Tape 140 - GTE, KCOP, 1992 Oct 24, 10:00 AM., 1992-10-24; 136
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 140)
  - Tape 141 - GLH Formula No, 9, WPIX-TV, 1992 Oct 24, 6:30 AM; Big Green Clean Machine, WPIX-TV, 1992 Oct 24, 7:00 AM; Choose to Be Healthy, WPIX-TV, 1992 Oct 24, 7:30 AM., 1992-10-24; 137
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 141)
  - Tape 142 - Oxygen Cocktail, WWOR-TV, 1992 Oct 24, 12:30 AM., 1992-10-24; 138
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 142)
  - Tape 143 - C&P Telephone--The Ringers, WBFF, 1992 Nov 10, 9:30 AM., 1992-11-10; 139
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 143)
  - Tape 144 - Zero Pain, TNN, 1992 Oct 24, 8:00 AM., 1992-10-24; 140
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 144)
  - Tape 145 - How to Succeed Without a Job, WPIX-TV, 1992 Oct 17, 6:30 AM; Firmflex, WPIX-TV, 1992 Oct 17, 7:00 AM; New Juice Man, WPIX-TV, 1992 Oct 17, 7:30 AM., 1992-10-17; 141
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 145)
  - Tape 146 - J, A, Alternatives, WWOR-TV, 1992 Oct 25, 8:00 AM., 1992-10-25; 142
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 146)
  - Tape 147 - Deal a Meal, WWOR-TV, 1992 Oct 25, 8:00 AM; Psychic Friends Network, WWOR-TV, 1992 Oct 25, 8:30 AM; Miracle Blade II, WWOR-TV, 1992 Oct 25, 9:00 AM; Dave del Dotto, WWOR-TV, 1992 Oct 25, 9:30 AM., 1992-10-25; 143
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 147)
  - Tape 148-151 - Quik Cook, WNYW-TV, 1992 Oct 11, 11:00 AM; Braun--A Winning Smile, WWOR-TV, 1992 Nov 21, 9:00 AM; Deni Turbo-Seal, WGBO-TV, 1991 Sep 28, 7:30 AM; Quick 'n Brite, WTVX, 1991 Sep 22, 12:00 PM., 1991-09-22/1992-11-21; 144
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 148-151)
  - Tape 152 - McDougal, WPIX-TV, 1992 Nov 14, 7:30 AM; Acne Statin, WWOR-TV, 1992 Nov 20, 9:00 AM; Cross Walk, WPIX-TV, 1992 Nov 14, 8:00 AM; Psychic Friends Network, WWOR-TV, 1992 Nov 28, 7:00 AM., 1992-11-14/1992-11-28; 145
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 152)
  - Tape 153 - Radio Shack Memorex, WPIX-TV, 1992 Dec 5, 8:00 AM; Making Money, WWOR-TV, 1992 Dec 5, 7:00 AM; Braun Slimline, WWOR-TV, 1992 Dec 5, 9:00 AM; Regal Shop, WNBC-TV, 1992 Dec 5, 1:30 PM., 1992-12-05; 146
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 153)
  - Tape 154 - Golfing Breakthrough for the 90s, WNBC-TV, 1992 Dec 5, 2:30 PM; Lifeline Gym, WNBC-TV, 1992 Dec 5, 3:30 PM; Quik and Easy Skin Care, WNYW-TV, 1992 Dec 23, 1:00 PM; Incredible Sweater Machine, WNBC-TV, 1992 Dec 23, 2:00 PM., 1992-12-05/1992-12-23; 147
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 154)
  - Tape 155 - Natural Trim, WWOR-TV, 1992 Dec 26, 8:30 AM; Redkin, WWOR-TV, 1992 Dec 26, 9:00 AM; Stop the Insanity, WWOR-TV, 1992 Dec 26, 9:30 AM; Phase Out the Smoke, WWOR-TV, 1992 Dec 26, 11:30 AM., 1992-12-26; 148
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 155)
  - Tape 156 - Lori Davis Hair, WWOR-TV, 1993 Jan 2, 8:00 AM; Fit 1 Exercise Machine, WWOR-TV, 1993 Jan 9, 7:30 AM; California Diet Plan, WWOR-TV, 1993 Jan 9, 11:00 AM; Edgar Morris Skin Care, WWOR-TV, 1993 Jan 16, 8:30 AM., 1993-01-02/1993-01-16; 149
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 156)
  - Tape 157 - Lasting Kiss, WWOR-TV, 1993 Jan 30, 2:30 AM; VCR Voice Programme, WPIX-TV, 1993 Jan 23, 7:00 AM; J, A, Alternatives, WWOR-TV, 1993 Jan 31, 8:00 AM; Financial Fitness, WNYW-TV, 1993 Feb 01, 1:00 PM., 1993-01-30/1993-02-01; 150
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 5, Video-cassette Tape 157)
  - Tape 158 - Rags to Riches, WWOR-TV, 1993 Feb 7, 8:00 AM; Wealth Building Workshop, WCBS, 1993 Feb 14, 7:30 AM; Jet Aire Hair Styling, WPIX-TV, 1993 Feb 27, 8:30 AM; Sterling Home Water Filter, WPIX-TV, 1993 Mar 6, 9:30 AM., 1993-02-07/1993-03-06; 151
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0001)
  - Tape 159 - Redken PDTS, WWOR-TV, 1993 Mar 13, 9:30 AM; Butterfly Ladder, WNYW-TV, 1993 Mar 14, 11:30 AM; Charles J, Givens, WNYW-TV, 1993 Mar 20, 3:00 PM; I, Q, Unlimited Computer, WWOR-TV, 1993 Mar 27, 8:30 AM., 1993-03-13/1993-03-27; 152
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0002)
  - Tape 160 - Time Life Program Buy, WWOR-TV, 1993 Mar 6, 7:30 AM; Fitness Quest Stand-Up Batter, WWOR-TV, 1993 Apr 3, 7:30 AM; Hidden Key to Loving, WWOR-TV, 1993 Apr 3, 8:00 AM; Autofon Polish, TNN, 1993 Apr 9, 8:30 AM., 1993-03-06/1993-03-09; 153
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0003)
  - Tape 161 - Avon, KTVX, 1993 Feb 14, 7:00 AM; Ross Perot, WNBC-TV, 1993 Apr 25, 7:00 PM; Tony Little, WPIX-TV, 1993 Apr 24, 8:30 AM; Kountry Kickin',WPIX-TV, 1993 May 8, 8:00 AM., 1993-02-14/1993-05-08; 154
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0004)
  - Tape 162 - Making Money Secrets, WWOR-TV, 1993 May 8, 7:00 AM; Journey into the New, WWOR-TV, 1993 May 8, 9:00 AM; Kurtain and Kraft Home, WPIX-TV, 1993 May 15, 7:00 AM; United We Stand America, WNBC-TV, 1993 May 30, 8:00 PM., 1993-05-08/1993-05-30; 155
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0005)
  - Tape 163 - Perfect Smile, WWOR-TV, 1993 June 5, 10:00 AM; Psychic Friends Network, WWOR-TV, 1993 June 5, 11:00 AM; Dale Carnegie, WPIX-TV, 1993 June 12, 7:00 AM; Eez-Away Relief, WWOR-TV, 1993 June 5, 7:30 AM., 1993-06-05/1993-06-12; 156
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0006)
  - Tape 164 - Family Entertainment Network, No station, 1993 June 12, 7:30 AM; Charles J, Givens, No station, 1993 June 12, 4:00 PM; Super Charger, No station, 1993 June 27, 12:30 PM; Soloflex, No station, 1993 July 12, 11:30 AM., 1993-06-12/1993-06-27; 157
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0007)
  - Tape 165 - McDonald's, BET, 1993 July 17, 7:30 PM; Popeil Pasta Maker, CNBC, 1993 June 27, 5:30 AM; Norelco Satinelle, WWOR-TV, 1993 July 24, 8:30 AM; Marshall Fields, WGN, 1993 June 26, 6:30 AM., 1993-06-26/1993-07-24; 158
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0008)
  - Tape 166 - Microcrisp Microwave Wrap, WCBS, 1993 Aug 8, 12:00 PM; Regina Easy Pro Carpet Cleaner, WPIX-TV, 1993 Aug 7, 7:00 AM; St, Joseph's Indian School, WPIX-TV, 1993 Aug 7, 7:30 AM; Home Business Opportunities, WWOR-TV, 1993 Aug 7, 7:30 AM., 1993-08-07/1993-08-08; 159
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0009)
  - Tape 167 - Ask Mike Computer Tutor, WWOR-TV, 1993 Aug 21, 7:00 AM; Jet Steam Oven 3000T, WWOR-TV, 1993 Aug 21, 7:30 AM; Duralon, WPIX-TV, 1993 Aug 28, 7:00 AM; Rhino Records BillboardLifetime, 1993 Sep 5, 8:00 AM., 1993-08-21/1993-09-05; 160
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0010)
  - Tape 168 - Realm Fragrances by Erox, WWOR-TV, 1993 Sep 18, 1:30 AM; Gravity Edge, WCBS, 1993 Sep 12, 7:30 AM; Jet Stream Oven,WCIV, 1993 Aug 7, 12:00 PM; Refractive Surgery, WCPO, 1993 Sep 19, 10:30 AM., 1993-08-07/1993-09-19; 161
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0011)
  - Tape 169 - Nothin' but Nets, WWOR-TV, 1993 Sep 28, 6:00 AM; Philips CDI, WWOR-TV, 1993 Sep 18, 9:00 AM; Interactive Network, WGBO-TV, 1993 Sep 26, 7:00 AM; Autofon Polish, WGBO-TV, 1993 Sep 26, 8:00 AM., 1993-09-18/1993-09-28; 162
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0012)
  - Tape 170 - Biogime Skin Care, WFLD, 1993 Oct 3, 9:30 AM; The World of Peter Rabbit, WWOR-TV, 1993 Sep 25, 10:00 AM; Psychic Friends Network, WNYW-TV, 1993 Sep 26, 11:30 AM; Mini Max, WPIX-TV, 1993 Oct 9, 8:30 AM., 1993-09-25/1993-10-09; 163
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0013)
  - Tape 171 - Buns of Steel, WNYW-TV, 1993 Nov 14, 11:00 AM; Snackmaster Dehydrator, WWOR-TV, 1993 Nov 13, 8:00 AM; Stop the Insanity, WWOR-TV, 1993 Nov 6, 7:30 AM; Skewdriver Pro Kit, WWOR-TV, 1993 Oct 9, 8:30 PM., 1993-10-09/1993-11-14; 164
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0014)
  - Tape 172 - Wilton's Let's Decorate, WWOR-TV, 1993 Oct 9, 10:00 AM; St Go Forever Young, WWOR-TV, 1993 Oct 16, 7:30 AM; Personal Power Program, WWOR-TV, 1993 Oct 16, 9:30 AM; Soloflex, WNYW-TV, 1993 Dec 7, 1:00 PM., 1993-10-09/1993-12-07; 165
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0015)
  - Tape 173 - Marshall Fields, WGN, 1993 June 26, 6:30 AM; Nordic Flex Gold exercise machine, WWOR-TV, 1993 Dec 4, 8:00 AM; Bissell Little Green, WWOR-TV, 1993 Dec 11, 7:30AM; Edgar Morris Skin Care, WWOR-TV, 1993 Dec 12, 5:00 AM., 1993-06-26/1993-12-12; 166
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0016)
  - Tape 175 - Fitness Breakthrough, Lifetime, 1994 Jan 2, 8:29 AM; Pro-Form Cross Trainer, WWOR-TV, 1994 Jan 1, 8:00 AM; Principal Secrets--Victoria Principal, WWOR-TV, 1994 Jan 10, 10:30 AM; Consumer Infoline, WWOR-TV, 1994 Jan 8, 7:30 AM., 1994-01-01/1994-01-10; 167
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0017)
  - Tape 176 - Desert Beauty Time, WWOR-TV, 1994 Jan 8, 9:00 AM; Mega Memory Photographic Memory, WWOR-TV, 1994 Jan 8, 8:30 AM; Kellogg's Just Right, CBS, 1994 Jan 11, 1:16 PM; Psychic Friends Network, WPIX-TV, 1994 Jan 15, 7:30 AM., 1994-01-08/1994-01-15; 168
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0018)
  - Tape 177 - Dual-Action Acne Regimen, Lifetime, 1994 Jan 23, 3:00 AM; Braun PDTS Oral B Plaque Remover, WWOR-TV, 1994 Jan 22, 8:30 AM., 1994-01-22/1994-01-23; 169
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0019)
  - Tape 178 - Video Professor, WPIX-TV, 1994 Jan 22, 7:00 AM; Health Rider, WCBS, 1994 Jan 29, 5:05 AM; Fantom Vacuum, WWOR-TV, 1994 Feb 5, 9:30 AM; Alex Langer Flying Lure, Family Channel, 1994 Mar 11, 3:00 AM., 1994-01-22/1994-03-11; 170
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 6, Video-cassette RL01062-VHS-0020)